We've gotta get rid of the body now.
Pato. you're sure she had no pulse?
I touched her neck. and there was nothing.
This isn't a game. Pato.
Nobody can find out about this. Got it?
It stays between us.
To our graves.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
ONE MONTH EARLIER
What I gotta do when I look at you
I wanna laugh out loud
Don't be cruel
What I gotta do when I look at…
Baby. you're mine
-Yeah? All right.
-Good. I appreciate it.
Okay. guys. Quiet down.
Class is in session.
All righty. so as you know.
we're nearing the end of the school year.
Most of you are about to graduate.
and I'm gonna miss you all so very much.
I'm kidding.
Okay. Enough with the waterworks.
Today we're going to be checking in
on your projects for the final.
Tamara. I know you and Daniel
decided to work together on the final.
Why don't you share with the class?
Uh. yeah. we're doing a documentary thing
on cyberbullying.
Quiet. guys.
Yeah. Tamara and I are making
a documentary.
And it's gonna be put together
like found footage
to explore cyberbullying at its most--
Shut up. nerd!
The main creative premise
is that the filmmaker.
as an impartial observer.
is thus impartial
to the horrors that plague us.
Great. Daniel.
Patricio. wanna say anything?
No. nothing. It's just…
I mean. I'm sorry. He just talks a lot.
I don't know. bro.
I'd watch any movie that had Tamara.
Ooh!
-Guys…
-She's always got something to say. right?
While I appreciate
your interest in their project. Xavi.
I'm more interested in hearing
about your project.
Well. obviously. I don't have a project.
Well. you need to do one
to pass the class. Xavi.
Don't you wanna graduate?
Don't you care about your future?
Why don't you research
your girlfriend's extracurriculars?
Silence! Xavier!
Everyone calm down. please.
Stop it. You're making it worse. Xavi.
Okay. that's it for today.
Catch up on your reading.
and remember to review
the previous two chapters.
All right? See you on Thursday.
LADY CHATTERLEY'S LOVER
Not all right on the wheel
We got a raw deal…
KILL YOURSELF. WEIRDO
TOTALLY GROSS
YOUR DAD WOULD BE ASHAMED
YOU'RE SO CRINGE
You're still up here?
Take a break. hon. I've hardly seen you.
But I've got a lot of homework.
-Well. come down and eat something.
-I'm not hungry. Ma.
-Thanks. though.
-Okay.
First. we do this side…
HI FROM ARGENTINA!
THERE'S THE MASTER!
YOU'RE THE KING!
Then move to the other.
COPIED AND SAVING…
Somebody asked me if this hurts to do.
Yes. It's painful to chisel.
But when it hurts.
that means it's working.
Hey. What you doing?
-Nothing. I'm researching. How 'bout you?
-Just editing… and doom scrolling.
Have you been able to find anything?
The document's still empty.
and we're short on time.
I don't know. Dani.
Do you think we're focusing
too much on the victims?
I mean. well.
it's supposed to be impartial.
Like a montage
about the horrors of the internet.
Just observation. no judgment.
Right. but I wonder if we should do
something more… immersive. you know?
We could connect different points of view
to contrast the victim and victimizer.
What are you thinking?
Hmm. What if we tried to speak to Xavi?
Xavi?
All right. you guys got this.
See you soon.
Hell yeah. man!
This video's gonna be a hit! Ooh.
Hell yeah.
Hey. what was that thing
with the goth girl in class earlier?
Tamara? I'm. uh…
gonna do my project on her.
What do you mean?
You don't have a project.
Look. Pato. every senior
at Campos Academy has a project to do.
I'm just choosing something
a little less… academic. y'know?
What's the project. huh?
-To take Tamara's virginity. bro.
-Bro. be serious.
The weirdo.
No way!
What about Samantha?
Samantha's been making some bad decisions.
And. well. to be honest.
revenge is sounding pretty good.
She's gonna lose her shit. bro!
Whatever.
Bro. it's Tamara.
She joined my live today.
God. it's like hunting.
All I'm saying is that
by interviewing Xavi.
our argument will be stronger.
by his perspective
being different. That's all.
Tam. 'Kay. Xavi hits his face
with a hammer in order to look more manly.
He's not much deeper than that.
Oh. I know. But then in class.
someone was making fun of the fact
that his girlfriend cheated on him. right?
The victimizer becomes the victim.
GIN_GWAI HAS TAGGED YOU IN A POST
Tam?
Tamara. get ready! Tamara. get ready!
What the fuck?
Tamara. get ready!
You good. Tam? You sound distracted.
-Yeah. I'm good. Just some freaks online.
-They still bothering you?
Oh. what?
KINGXAVI HAS SENT YOU 2 MESSAGES
-What is it?
-Oh! Nothing. Nothing.
-Tam?
-Uh…
Call you back in a bit. okay?
-Okay. but…
-'Kay.
What's up?
Hey. I was thinking about how I'd love
to be a part of your documentary.
I don't have a final project.
so would it be cool if I joined yours
or something?
No! Are you serious. dude?
Yeah. you're supposed to say nice things.
tell her she's pretty.
kiss her on the forehead.
make her feel really good.
-That's all it takes.
-Shit. dude. really?
-I'm the master.
-That's psychopathic.
You're crazy. man.
Watch and learn.
But don't tell anyone.
It's just between you and me.
Okay?
FINAL PROJECT
Hey
I love the green
I love the pink and blue
I love the red and yellow too
And I love you!
I love the sun
I like the rainfall too
I love the sea. I love the sky
I love the storm. and I love you
Subtitle translation by: Meredith Cannella
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm